[{"question": "<p>What will be the output of the following code:</p><br><p><code>x = np.array([4, 3, 2, 1])<br>for I in x:<br>    print(I)</code></p>", "type": "multiple_choice", "answers": [{"answer": "error", "correct": false}, {"answer": "4, 3, 2, 1", "correct": true}, {"answer": "1, 2, 3, 4", "correct": false}, {"answer": "I, I, I, I", "correct": false}], "tag": "arrays", "lecture_file": "02_integration_1"}, {"question": "For x = np.array([1, 2, 3, 4, 5]), what is x[-2]", "type": "multiple_choice", "answers": [{"answer": "-1", "correct": false}, {"answer": "1", "correct": false}, {"answer": "4", "correct": true}, {"answer": "5", "correct": false}], "tag": "arrays", "lecture_file": "02_integration_1"}, {"question": "For x = np.array([1, 2, 3, 4, 5]), what is x[::-1]", "type": "multiple_choice", "answers": [{"answer": "array([5])", "correct": false}, {"answer": "array([5, 4, ,3, 2, 1])", "correct": true}, {"answer": "array([5, 5, 5, 5, 5 ])", "correct": false}, {"answer": "array([-1])", "correct": false}], "tag": "arrays", "lecture_file": "02_integration_1"}, {"question": "<p>Given</p><br><pre><code>a = np.linspace(0, 5, 2)<br>b = np.linspace(5, 10, 3)<br>c = np.linspace(10, 15, 5)<br><br>A, _ = np.meshgrid(a, b, c)<br></code></pre><br><p>What is the shape of the array A?</p>", "type": "multiple_choice", "answers": [{"answer": "(3, 2, 5)", "correct": true}, {"answer": "(5, 5, 5)", "correct": false}, {"answer": "(2, 3, 5)", "correct": false}, {"answer": "(5, 3, 2)", "correct": false}], "tag": "arrays", "lecture_file": "04_fode_2"}, {"question": "<pre><code>A = np.array([[1, 2, 3], [4, 5, 6], [7, 8, 9]])<br>B = np.array([1, 1, 1])<br></code></pre><br><p>What is the shape of 'A+B'?</p>", "type": "multiple_choice", "answers": [{"answer": "(3, 3)", "correct": true}, {"answer": "(1, 3)", "correct": false}, {"answer": "(3, 1)", "correct": false}, {"answer": "(1, 1)", "correct": false}], "tag": "arrays", "lecture_file": "04_fode_2"}, {"question": "<pre><code>A = np.array([[1, 2, 3], [4, 5, 6], [7, 8, 9]])<br>B = np.array([1])<br></code></pre><br><p>What is the value of 'A+B'?</p>", "type": "multiple_choice", "answers": [{"answer": "np.array([[2, 2, 3], [5, 5, 6], [8, 8, 9]])", "correct": false}, {"answer": "ValueError: operands could not be broadcast together with shapes (3,3) (1,) ", "correct": false}, {"answer": "np.array([[2, 3, 4], [5, 6, 7], [8, 9, 10]])", "correct": true}, {"answer": "np.array([[2, 3, 4], [4, 5, 6], [7, 8, 9]])", "correct": false}], "tag": "arrays", "lecture_file": "04_fode_2"}, {"question": "What will be the value of b: <br><br>a = np.linspace(6, 10, 5)<br>b = *a", "type": "multiple_choice", "answers": [{"answer": "Memory address of 'a'", "correct": false}, {"answer": "6.0  7.0  8.0  9.0  10.0", "correct": false}, {"answer": "SyntaxError", "correct": true}, {"answer": "np.array([6.0, 7.0, 8.0, 9.0, 10.0])", "correct": false}], "tag": "arrays", "lecture_file": "04_fode_2"}, {"question": "What is the output of:<br><br>a = np.linspace(6, 10, 5)<br>print(*a)", "type": "multiple_choice", "answers": [{"answer": "Memory address of 'a'", "correct": false}, {"answer": "6.0  7.0  8.0  9.0  10.0", "correct": true}, {"answer": "SyntaxError", "correct": false}, {"answer": "np.array([6.0, 7.0, 8.0, 9.0, 10.0])", "correct": false}], "tag": "arrays", "lecture_file": "04_fode_2"}, {"question": "What will be the output of X[:, 2], where<br>X = np.array([[1, 2, 3], [4, 5, 6], [7, 8, 9]])", "type": "multiple_choice", "answers": [{"answer": "array([4, 5, 6])", "correct": false}, {"answer": "array([2, 5, 8])", "correct": false}, {"answer": "array([1, 2])", "correct": false}, {"answer": "array([3, 6, 9])", "correct": true}], "tag": "arrays", "lecture_file": "04_fode_2"}, {"question": "A = np.array([[12, 15], [18, 21]])<br>B = np.array([6, 3])<br>A / B = ?", "type": "multiple_choice", "answers": [{"answer": "np.array([[2, 5], [18, 21]])", "correct": false}, {"answer": "np.array([[12, 15], [3, 7]])", "correct": false}, {"answer": "Error", "correct": false}, {"answer": "np.array([[2, 5], [3, 7]])", "correct": true}], "tag": "arrays", "lecture_file": "15_intro_linear_algebra"}]